(Bernadette:)I'm clearly upset.
Why aren't you following me?
Sorry! Sorry!
(Bert:)And when Amy started using
a solution of chromic acid
(Bert:)and white vinegar to clean
all her lab equipment,
(Bert:)all of a sudden,
everybody was doing it.
You trend setter!
(Amy:)Just the right idea
at the right time.
(Penny:)Okay, okay, so Amy's cool,
Sheldon's cool.
(Penny:)Tell me about Leonard.
Who?
(Penny:)Leonard Hofstadter.
(Bert:)Oh, him.
I guess he's all right.
(Bert:)Apparently he tricked some
hot girl into marrying him.
(Penny:)That's me, I'm her.
(Penny:)You know, he
didn't trick me.
(Penny:)He just wore me down.
(Bert:)It makes sense
you two are friends.
(Bert:)I mean, hot girls
always stick together.
(Amy:)And you thought this
wasn't gonna be
(Amy:)a great party.